<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days App</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">This app uses The Movie Database (TMDb) API for content but is not endorsed or certified by TMDb.</string>
    <string name="day1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day30">Day 30</string>
    <string name="day31">Day 31</string>

    <string name="movie_day1">The Conjuring 1 &amp; 2</string>
    <string name="theme_sunday">(Spooky Sunday)</string>

    <string name="movie_day2">Inception</string>
    <string name="theme_monday">(Mind-Bending Monday by Nolan)</string>

    <string name="movie_day3">Kill Bill Vol. 1 &amp; 2</string>
    <string name="theme_tuesday">(Tarantino Tuesday)</string>

    <string name="movie_day4">The Green Book</string>
    <string name="theme_wednesday">(Wholesome Wednesday)</string>

    <string name="movie_day5">Back to the Future</string>
    <string name="theme_thursday">(Throwback Thursday)</string>

    <string name="movie_day6">Se7en</string>
    <string name="theme_friday">(Fincher Friday)</string>

    <string name="movie_day7">The Hangover Trilogy</string>
    <string name="theme_saturday">(Satirical Saturday)</string>

    <string name="movie_day8">It &amp; It 2</string>

    <string name="movie_day9">Interstellar</string>

    <string name="movie_day10">Pulp Fiction</string>

    <string name="movie_day11">Bruce Almighty</string>

    <string name="movie_day12">The Breakfast Club</string>

    <string name="movie_day13">Fight Club</string>

    <string name="movie_day14">Rush Hour Trilogy</string>

    <string name="movie_day15">The Ring Trilogy</string>

    <string name="movie_day16">Shutter Island</string>

    <string name="movie_day17">Django Unchained</string>

    <string name="movie_day18">Forrest Gump</string>

    <string name="movie_day19">Shawshank Redemption</string>

    <string name="movie_day20">Zodiac</string>

    <string name="movie_day21">Hot Fuzz</string>

    <string name="movie_day22">28 Days Later</string>

    <string name="movie_day23">Tenet</string>

    <string name="movie_day24">Inglourious Basterds</string>

    <string name="movie_day25">Amélie</string>

    <string name="movie_day26">Ferris Bueller’s Day Off</string>

    <string name="movie_day27">Gone Girl</string>

    <string name="movie_day28">The Interview</string>

    <string name="movie_day29">Hereditary</string>

    <string name="movie_day30">Memento</string>

    <string name="movie_day31">Reservoir Dogs</string>

    <string name="day1_desc">Paranormal investigators Ed and Lorraine Warren confront sinister forces in two spine-chilling cases involving a haunted farmhouse and a family possessed by dark spirits. (The Conjuring 1 &amp; 2)</string>
    <string name="day2_desc">A skilled thief who steals secrets from within the subconscious must now achieve the impossible: plant an idea in someone’s mind through a complex dream heist. (Inception)</string>
    <string name="day3_desc">A betrayed assassin awakens from a coma and embarks on a relentless journey of bloody vengeance against her ex-lover and his deadly gang. (Kill Bill Vol. 1 &amp; 2)</string>
    <string name="day4_desc">Amélie, a whimsical Parisian waitress, finds joy in helping others discover happiness while secretly navigating her own journey toward love and belonging. (Amélie)</string>
    <string name="day5_desc">Teenager Marty McFly accidentally travels to 1955 and must ensure his teenage parents fall in love, or risk being erased from existence. (Back to the Future)</string>
    <string name="day6_desc">Two detectives with contrasting personalities chase a sadistic serial killer who uses the seven deadly sins as the basis for his horrific crimes. (Se7en)</string>
    <string name="day7_desc">Three friends wake up from wild bachelor parties with no memory of the night before, and must retrace their steps in a hilarious series of misadventures. (The Hangover Trilogy)</string>

    <string name="day8_desc">A group of children are haunted by a demonic clown that preys on their fears, returning decades later for a terrifying showdown. (It)</string>
    <string name="day9_desc">With Earth on the brink of collapse, a group of astronauts travel through a wormhole to explore distant planets and find hope for humanity\'s survival. (Interstellar)</string>
    <string name="day10_desc">An unforgettable blend of intertwined stories featuring hitmen, a boxer, and gangsters in Los Angeles, all tied together by sharp dialogue and brutal twists. (Pulp Fiction)</string>
    <string name="day11_desc">A frustrated man is temporarily granted divine powers, learning that being God isn’t as easy as it seems and discovering what truly matters in life. (Bruce Almighty)</string>
    <string name="day12_desc">Five high school students from different backgrounds share personal revelations and forge unexpected friendships during Saturday detention. (The Breakfast Club)</string>
    <string name="day13_desc">An insomniac office worker and a mysterious soap salesman start a secret fight club, but it soon spirals into something far more dangerous. (Fight Club)</string>

    <string name="day14_desc">A street-smart LAPD detective and a disciplined Hong Kong inspector team up, battling crime and cultural clashes in hilarious and action-packed ways. (Rush Hour Trilogy)</string>
    <string name="day15_desc">A cursed videotape leads to sudden and terrifying deaths unless its deadly secret is unraveled. A journalist races against time to uncover the mystery. (Ring Trilogy)</string>
    <string name="day16_desc">A U.S. Marshal investigating a patient\'s disappearance at a mental asylum discovers shocking truths about the facility—and himself. (Shutter Island)</string>    <string name="day17_desc">A freed slave partners with a German bounty hunter to rescue his wife from a sadistic plantation owner in the antebellum South. (Django Unchained)</string>
    <string name="day18_desc">Forrest Gump, a simple man with a big heart, unintentionally shapes historic events while searching for love and understanding. (Forrest Gump)</string>
    <string name="day19_desc">When a theme park filled with cloned dinosaurs malfunctions, visitors must survive a deadly prehistoric nightmare. (Jurassic Park)</string>
    <string name="day20_desc">A cartoonist becomes obsessed with identifying the elusive Zodiac Killer, risking his safety and sanity in the process. (Zodiac)</string>

    <string name="day21_desc">A sharp London cop is reassigned to a sleepy village, where he uncovers a dark conspiracy behind a series of bizarre accidents. (Hot Fuzz)</string>
    <string name="day22_desc">A mysterious virus turns people into violent, rage-filled creatures, and a handful of survivors must navigate a decimated Britain. (28 Days Later)</string>
    <string name="day23_desc">In a world where time flows in reverse, a secret agent must use inversion to prevent a catastrophe that could end humanity. (Tenet)</string>
    <string name="day24_desc">A group of Jewish-American soldiers known as “The Basterds” plot to assassinate Nazi leaders during WWII, sparking a brutal and explosive revenge tale. (Inglourious Basterds)</string>
    <string name="day25_desc">On a concert tour through the 1960s American South, a black pianist and his Italian-American driver form an unlikely and enduring friendship. (Green Book)</string>
    <string name="day26_desc">High schooler Ferris Bueller skips school for a legendary day of fun and chaos around Chicago, inspiring those around him to live fully. (Ferris Bueller’s Day Off)</string>
    <string name="day27_desc">A man’s life unravels as suspicion and media frenzy erupt after his wife goes missing, revealing secrets and lies in their troubled marriage. (Gone Girl)</string>

    <string name="day28_desc">Two bumbling journalists are recruited by the CIA to assassinate North Korea’s leader during a televised interview, with hilarious and explosive consequences. (The Interview)</string>
    <string name="day29_desc">After the death of their reclusive grandmother, a family is haunted by horrifying secrets and a legacy of supernatural terror. (Hereditary)</string>
    <string name="day30_desc">A man with short-term memory loss meticulously tracks clues on his body to hunt the man responsible for his wife’s murder. (Memento)</string>
    <string name="day31_desc">A jewelry heist goes violently wrong, unraveling the loyalty, lies, and hidden identities among a gang of criminals in Quentin Tarantino’s explosive debut. (Reservoir Dogs)</string>

</resources>